const STORE = [
    {
          question: 'What is the first rule of CrossFit?',
          answers: [
              'Always talk about CrossFit!',
              'Always eat paleo.',
              'Always do everything Rich Froning says.',
              'Always buy everthing that says Reebok CrossFit on it.'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'Always talk about CrossFit!'
      },
      {
          question: 'What are 4 correct points of performance of an air squat?',
          answers: [
              'Hips descend back and down, hips descend lower than knees, knees track over toes, and lumbar curve is maintained.', 
              'Hips descend lower than kneess, hips descend back and down, feet are placed wider than shoulder witdth, elbows remain locked out.', 
              'Hips descend lower than knees, complete full hip and knee extension at the top of mvmt, feet are placed together, heels come off the gorund at top of the movement.',
              'Hips descend lower than the knees, heels are not in contact with the ground, shoulders are engaged, and lumbar curve maintained.',
              ],
              correctAnswer:'Hips descend back and down, hips descend lower than knees, knees track over toes, and lumbar curve is maintained.'
      },
      {
          question: 'If you have a beginner athlete that is peforming a clean and is pulling early, has their knees caved in at the bottom of the squat and also has loss of lumbar curve at the bottom of the squat - what do you fix first?',
          answers: [
              'Fix all 3 movement faults in one cue.', 
              'Only fix the early arm bend.', 
              'Fix the loss of lumbar curve at the bottom of the squat.', 
              'Fix the knee cave in and early arm bend.'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'Fix the loss of lumbar curve at the bottom of the squat.'
      },
      {
          question: 'Todays WOD is Helen - you have an athlete that can crank out 3-5 kipping pull ups at a time under fatigue - we want all our athletes to finish within a 15 min max time frame. What scaling option do you give them?</br></br>Helen RX</br>3 Rounds for Time:</br>400m run </br> 21 kettle bell swings </br>12 pull ups', 
          answers: [
              'Do it RX anyway. ALL THE INTENSITY ALL OF THE TIME!',
              'Drop the pull up reps to 8.', 
              'Tell the athlete to do as many reps as they can RX, then switch to ring rows when they hit failure.',
              'Tell the athlete to do push ups instead because they are better at the movememnt anyway.',
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'Drop the pull up reps to 8.'
      },
      {
          question: 'What is the most common cause of injury in a CrossFit Gym?',
          answers: [
              'Lifting heavy weights.',
              'Handstand push ups.',
              'Squatting below parallel.',
              'Agro boxes'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'Agro boxes'
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the proper progression for a Sumo Deadlift High Pull?',
        answers: [
            'Sumo DL, Sumo DL + shoulder shrug slow, sumo DL + shoulder shrug at speed, sumo DL high pull.',
            'High pull, sumo DL + shoulder shrug fast, sumo DL high pull.',
            'Regular DL, sumo DL, sumoe DL high pull',
            'Regular DL, high pull, DL high pull'
        ], 
        correctAnswer: 'Sumo DL, Sumo DL + shoulder shrug slow, sumo DL + shoulder shrug at speed, sumo DL high pull.'
  
      },
      {
          question:'You have the work out Fran to coach today and you have an athlete who has an injured wrist and it hurts to do barbell thrusters, what scaling options do you give them?',
          answers: [
              'Power through the pain! no pain no gain!', 
              'Tell them to leave the thrusters out and only do the pull ups.',
              'Have them do 1 arm thrusters wit a weight that will provide the same stimulous as the barbell.',
              'Tell them they should not be working out.'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'Have them do 1 arm thrusters wit a weight that will provide the same stimulous as the barbell.'
      },
      {
          question: 'Name this work out: For time: 5 rounds\
          15 over head squats (95/65)\
          400m run',
          answers: [
              'Helen',
              'Nancy',
              'Randy',
              'Grace'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'Nancy',
      },
      {
       question: 'If an athlete is not extending their hips and knees during a push jerk and you have already verbally cued them, what are your next options?', 
       answers: [
           'Ignore the problem, their movement isnst that bad anyway.',
           'Say the same thing over and over again until the athlete understands. Be relentless!!',
           'Take them out from under the bar and give a tactile cue.',
           'Tell them to squat because they are better at that anway.'    
       ],
       correctAnswer: 'Take them out from under the bar and give a tactile cue.'
              
      },
      {
          question: 'What are 3 ways to reduce rhabdomyloysis during a work out?',
          answers: [
              'Rhabdo is not really an issue',
              'Familiarize yourself with the types of exercises and evniornmental conditions that are more likely to cause rhabdo. As well as the types of athletse that are most lilely to get rhabdo.',
              'Tell athletes to eat paleo.',
              'Tell athletes to drink Kill Cliff to avoid rhabdo.'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'Familiarize yourself with the types of exercises and evniornmental conditions that are more likely to cause rhabdo. As well as the types of athletse that are most lilely to get rhabdo',
      }
  ];